嘿 我都打包好了 随时可以走
Hey! I'm all packed and ready to go.
没错 爹地跟乔伊叔叔 今天要出门去
Oh, that's right. Daddy and Uncle Joey are going on a trip today.
我们要去参加 一个在巴贝多的研讨会 对不对？
We're going to a conference in Barbados. Right?
- 额   - 你会说"巴贝多"吗？
- Uh-huh.     - Can you say, "Barbados"?
巴贝多
Barbados.
我觉得 要你们到那么远的地方去…
Okay. I've gotta say, it means so much to me that you guys are coming...
听我的演讲 对我真是意义重大
all the way over there to hear me give my speech.
我要让你们高兴一下 我费尽功夫…
Ooh, and I have a surprise. I had to pull some strings...
帮大家争取拿到整个研讨会的通行证 没错
but I was able to get everyone passes to the entire conference. That's right!
这些宝贝可以让你们自由参加 所有的古生物学演讲或是研讨会
These babies will get you into all the paleontology lectures and seminars.
你有什么东西 是可以让我们不用参加的吗？
Do you have anything that will get us out of them?
能听你的演讲 我们真的很兴奋 但是其他的时间…
We're excited to hear the speech, but the rest of the time...
我们想要做其他岛上的活动
we're gonna want to do island stuff.
大卫或许会想要听几场演说
David'll probably want to hear a few lectures.
- 没错 因为他是科学家   - 不 不是
- Right, because he's a scientist.     - No, no.
他在明斯克待了八年 如果在阳光下待太久…
He's been in Minsk for eight years. If he gets too much direct sunlight...
他会死的
he'll die.
- 好 我们该出发了   - 是吗？
- Okay, we'd better go.     - Yeah?
- 那我们明天见   - 好的 明天见
- So we'll see you guys tomorrow.     - All right, let's do it.
跟查莉一起飞五个小时 喝几杯酒…
A five-hour flight with Charlie, have a couple drinks...
在毛毯下做一些自然会发生的事
get under that blanket and do what comes natural.
那是毛毯 乔伊 不是隐形披风
It's a blanket, Joe, not a cloak of invisibility.
- 哇 这地方真漂亮   - 瞧瞧这些古生物学家
- Wow, this place is beautiful!     - Look at all these paleontologists!
对啊 明天游泳池旁 一定有许多苍白的人
I know. There are gonna be some pasty folks by the pool tomorrow.
我的天啊 我不敢相信你在这里
Oh, my God, I can't believe you're here!
我想我被认出来了
I think I've been recognized.
- 这常常发生   - 盖勒博士？我真是仰慕你
- This happens all the time.     - Dr. Geller? I am such a huge fan.
这倒是从来没有发生过
That never happens.
我多年来一直很注意你的研究 我迫不及待要听你的演说
I've been following your career for years. I can't wait for your keynote speech.
- 哇 你太过奖了   - 能不能请你签名？
- Wow. This is very flattering...     - I would love your autograph.
喔 当然
Well, sure. Um...
- 亲爱的？ - 莎拉
- "Dear?"     - Sarah.
"莎拉 我挖(喜欢)你"
"Sarah. I dig you."
- "罗斯盖勒博士"   - 哇 真是太谢谢你了
- "Dr. Ross Geller."     - Oh, thank you so much.
不客气 莎拉 容我介绍一下 我的同事 魏勒教授
Sure. Sarah, I'd like you to introduce you to my colleague, Professor Wheeler.
- 这位是乔伊崔比亚尼   - 你是古生物学家吗？
- And this is Joey Tribbiani.     - Are you a paleontologist?
不 天啊 不是 我是演员
No, God, no, no. I'm an actor.
你或许有看过我… 演的一出小戏 叫做《那个我们的日子》
You probably recognize me from a little show called The Days of Our Lives.
老兄 是《我们的日子》 没有"那个"
Dude, it's just Days of Our Lives. There's no "the."
好吧 罗斯 天啊 你… 不 我扮演德瑞克雷莫瑞医生
Okay, Ross, boy, you... Yeah. No, no. I play Dr. Drake Ramoray.
- 很抱歉 我家没有电视   - 你家没有电视？
- I'm sorry. I don't own a TV.     - You don't own a TV?
那你家的家俱是摆向哪个方向？
What's all your furniture pointed at?
大卫 你可以帮个忙吗？
David, can you help me?
我正在跟钱德解释 飞机怎么能停留在空中
I'm trying to explain to Chandler how a plane stays in the air.
当然 那是伯努利原理加上…
Oh, certainly. That's a combination of Bernoulli's Principle...
- 牛顿第三运动定律   - 懂了？
- and Newton's third law of motion.     - See?
是啊 完全就是你所说的 "跟风有关"
Yeah. That's the same as, "It has something to do with wind."
我要去为这次旅行买几样东西
I'm gonna go pick up a few things for the trip.
我也应该走了 明天你们要一起搭计程车到机场吗？
I should go too. Now, tomorrow do you want to share a cab to the airport...
还是说我跟麦克到机场 跟你们碰面呢？
or should Mike and I meet you?
麦克？谁是麦克啊？
Mike? Who's Mike?
- 麦克是你的前男友   - 没错
- Mike's your ex-boyfriend.     - That's right!
哇 我已经完全忘掉他了
Oh, yeah. Wow, I had totally forgotten about him.
- 过去的事突然脱口而出   - 不 没关系 无心之过
- That's a blast from the past, huh?     - No, it's okay. Honest mistake.
那真的不代表什么 我是说 你知道的…
It really doesn't mean anything. I mean, you know...
摩妮卡也常常把钱德叫成理查
Monica refers to Chandler as Richard all the time.
- 她有吗？ - 我们快让你离开吧
- She does?     - Let's get you out of here.
至少你也拖我一起下水了
Well, at least you took me down with you.
我很抱歉 我只是… 我一直在想麦克
I'm so sorry. I just... I keep thinking about Mike.
我非常喜欢大卫 而且我们在一起很开心
I'm crazy about David, and we're having so much fun together.
为什么我会想念麦克？这真是… 这会消失的 对吗？
Why? Why do I miss Mike? That's just... That's gonna go away, right?
- 嗯 我猜是吧 总有一天   - 是啊
- Well, I guess. In time.     - Yeah.
我对理查的感觉已经消失了
I mean, my feelings for Richard are certainly gone.
你又来了 是钱德 你对钱德的感觉已经消失了
You just did it again. Chandler. Your feelings for Chandler are certainly gone.
天啊 菲比还在想麦克吗？
Boy, Phoebe's still pretty hung up on that Mike, huh?
要是我就不会想太多
I wouldn't read too much into it.
但是女生把你叫成 她前男友的名字…
Still, a girl calls you by her ex-boyfriend's name...
- 那不是什么好事 对不对？ - 让我先打断你一下
- that's not a good thing, right?     - Let me stop you there.
我想我知道这是怎么回事了 我不太擅长给人忠告
Because I think I see where this is going. I'm not very good at giving advice.
想要建议 最好去找罗斯或摩妮卡 如果你想了解…
See, if you want advice, go to Ross or Monica. Or Joey...
披萨馅料或是尿尿时 为何有灼热感 那就去找乔伊
for advice about pizza toppings or a burning sensation when you pee.
很抱歉 我只是希望能做点什么 你知道吗？
I'm sorry, I just wish there was something I could do, you know?
- 嗯 你知道菲比…   - 你真的想跟我谈这个吗？
- Well, you know Phoebe...     - Seriously, we're gonna do this?
很抱歉 我只希望 我能让她忘了麦克
I'm sorry, I just wish I could make her forget about Mike already.
- 菲比跟麦克为什么分手？ - 因为他的老二太大了
- Why did Phoebe and Mike break up?     - Oh, because his penis was too big.
抱歉 那才是我擅长的事
I'm sorry. That's the kind of thing I do.
他们分手 是因为麦克不想要结婚
They broke up because Mike didn't want to get married.
如果让菲比知道 你愿意结婚呢？
What if you let Phoebe know you'd be open to marriage?
太棒了 太棒了 我会跟她求婚
That's great. That's great. I'll propose to her.
什么？
What?
反正我迟早都会这么做的
I was probably going to do it at some point.
- 不 我没有说现在   - 为什么不呢？这实在太聪明了
- No, I didn't mean now.     - Well, why not? It's brilliant.
"再见 麦克 我们婚礼见 老兄
"Goodbye, Mike. We'll see you at the wedding, fella.
我们可能也不会 邀请你参加婚礼 但是…"
Well, we probably won't invite you to the wedding, but..."
- 衷心地谢谢你 钱德   - 不用客气
- Well, thank you, Chandler. Sincerely.     - Well, you're welcome.
很高兴能够帮得上忙
Glad I could help.
- 你认为我该怎么求婚呢？ - 大卫 我在假装看杂志
- How do you think I should propose?     - I'm pretending to read here.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你好吗？嘿 你好吗？
Yeah. How you doing?
- 嘿 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey, hey.     - Hey.
你说你要穿丁字裤的 丁字裤呢？
You said you were gonna wear a thong. Where's the thong?
我不是说丁字裤 我是说夹脚凉鞋
Ha, ha, I didn't mean a thong. I meant thongs.
你应该要说清楚的
You really should have been more clear about that.
你们绝对猜不出来 我在楼下看到谁
You're never gonna guess who I just saw downstairs.
小甜甜布兰妮
Oh, uh, uh, Britney Spears!
是啊 她绝对不会错过 这种研讨会的
Yeah. She never misses these conferences.
- 我刚刚看到肯尼斯史华兹博士   - 喔 我的天啊
- No, I just saw Dr. Kenneth Schwartz!     - Oh, my God!
- 对啊   - 你有跟他说话吗？
- I know!     - Did you talk to him?
是喔 我要跟 肯尼斯史华兹说什么？
Oh, yeah. What am I gonna say to Kenneth Schwartz?
你可以说"嗨 肯尼 为什么你不是小甜甜布兰妮？"
You could say, "Hey, Kenny, how come you're not Britney Spears?"
- 准备好要走了吗？ - 你现在就要走了？
- You ready to go?     - You're gonna go now?
- 我以为你可陪我一下   - 我不行 我整天都有研讨会
- I thought we could hang out.     - I can't. I have seminars all day.
我答应罗斯 我会看看他的演说稿
I promised Ross I'd look at his speech.
或许我们晚点可以一起 在阳台上吃晚餐 很浪漫哦
But maybe we could have dinner later? Out on the balcony? Lt'll be romantic.
你可以穿丁字裤吗？
Will you wear a thong?
你穿我就穿
I will if you will.
你的交换条件真是奇怪
You got yourself a very weird deal.
我很好 我晚餐已经有安排了
I'm good. I have dinner plans.
- 你一个人可以吗？ - 当然 可以
- So you gonna be okay?     - Yeah, yeah.
我有很多事可以做 我要去海滩 去游泳
I got tons of stuff I could do. I'm gonna hit the beach, go swimming.
乔伊 你有看看外面吗？
Joe, have you looked outside?
没有 为什么？
No. Why?
- 天啊   - 这里有室内游泳池
- Oh, man.     - There's an indoor pool.
- 你可以在那边游泳   - 是啊
- You could swim there.     - Yeah.
我没有要游泳 我是要去挖洞的
I wasn't gonna swim. I was gonna dig a hole.
麦克那件事真是有趣 我不知道…
That "Mike" was interesting. I don't know what's gonna happen...
- 菲比跟大卫之间会有什么事   - 我知道 要提示吗？
- with Phoebe and David.     - I do. Want a hint, huh?
我知 我知道
I do. I do.
好 我可以感觉到 这是某种文字游戏
Okay, I'm sensing this is some kind of wordplay...
因为你已经有点 无法控制 兴奋到脸红了
because you are pink with barely controlled glee.
- 大卫要跟菲比求婚   - 什么？为什么？
- David's gonna propose to Phoebe.     - What? Why?
因为我们本来在谈 他有哪些可以赢过麦克的方式
Because we were talking about ways he could beat Mike...
而我告诉他菲比想要结婚
and I told him Phoebe wanted to get married.
钱德 我们已经谈过了
Chandler, we have talked about this.
你不可以给别人建议
You are not supposed to give people advice!
你不能说一些 不得体的笑话就好了吗？
Couldn't you have made some inappropriate joke?
我说了 一个老二的笑话
I did! A penis one!
说明一下 我说的有什么不对？
Just so I know, what was so wrong about what I said?
他们才交往几个星期而已
They've only been going out for a few weeks.
菲比还无法忘记麦克 我想她会拒绝的
Phoebe is completely hung up on Mike. I mean, she'll say no...
然后大卫会心碎 他们会很难复合
David's heart will be broken, it'll be too hard for them to recover...
然后菲比又会孤单一个人
and then Phoebe will end up alone again.
天啊 真是糟糕的建议
Man, that's some bad advice.
感谢上帝 你们来了
Oh, hey. Thank God. You guys are here.
- 怎么了？ - 这里一切都不对劲
- What's going on?     - Everything is upside-down here.
整天都在下雨 没有人看电视 而且罗斯还很有名
It rains all day long and nobody watches TV, and Ross is famous.
我不想要惊动大家…
I don't want to alarm anybody...
但是摩妮卡的头发 比下飞机时膨了一倍
but Monica's hair is twice as big as it was when we landed.
我去湿度高的地方…
Okay. When I go places with high humidity...
头发就会比较蓬松 好吗？
it gets a little extra body, okay?
那就是为什么我们的蜜月照 看起来是我跟戴安娜罗丝
That's why our honeymoon photos look like me and Diana Ross.
我带你们去登记住房
I'll show you guys where to check in.
亲爱的 要确定我们可以拿到 超大尺寸的床哦
Oh, honey? Can you make sure we get a king-size bed?
大卫 也帮我们确定一下 还有看看他们有没有心型的床
Oh, David, get one for us too. Oh, and see if they have a heart-shaped one.
而且天花板上要有镜子
And with mirrors on the ceiling.
还有确定我们的房间 不要在他们的隔壁
And make sure our room isn't next to theirs.
喔 你们真幸运 有人陪你们来这里
Oh, you guys are so lucky you're here with people.
这是个很浪漫的地方
You know, it's just such a romantic place.
我只希望可以跟一个男人共享
I just wish I could share it with a guy.
- 不是跟乔伊   - 不是跟乔伊 不是
- Not Joey.     - Not Joey. No.
- 我只是在垂涎钱德   - 是噢
- I was just lusting after Chandler.     - Yeah, right.
我今晚要跟菲比求婚
So I'm proposing to Phoebe tonight.
今晚？
Tonight?
订婚戒指不是应该要有钻石吗？
Isn't an engagement ring supposed to have a diamond?
喔 在这里
Oh, there it is.
是啊 一个失败的科学家
Yes, well, being a failed scientist...
并没有像你想的赚那么多
doesn't pay quite as well as you might think.
那是七十分之一克拉
That's one-seventieth of a carat.
清晰度是很差
And the clarity is quite poor.
很好
Nice.
- 摩妮卡 我可以跟你谈一下吗？ - 好的
- Monica, can I talk to you for a second?     - Okay.
大卫要在今晚跟菲比求婚
David's gonna propose to Phoebe tonight.
你看 这就是你给别人建议的结果
See what happens when you give people advice?
- 我希望你有告诉他不可以   - 那也是一个建议
- Well, I hope you told him not to.     - That would be advice!
好 没关系 让我来处理
Okay, fine. I'll handle this.
- 菲比？ - 怎样？
- Phoebe?     - Yeah?
- 我需要跟你谈谈   - 你要离开《至上女声三重唱》？
- I need to talk to you.     - Are you leaving the Supremes?
我老公刚给了你男友 一个很糟糕的建议
Okay, my husband just gave your boyfriend some very bad advice.
大卫今晚要跟你求婚
David's gonna propose to you tonight.
哇 真的吗？
Wow, really?
这实在太棒了
That's fantastic!
什么？你是说真的吗？你想嫁给他？
What? Are you serious? You want to marry him?
- 那麦克呢？ - 是吗 你要我嫁给麦克吗？
- What about Mike?     - Oh, okay, you want me to marry Mike?
好啊 我们把他 嘴巴塞住 手铐铐上
Let's just gag him and handcuff him...
然后逼他踏上红毯 好吗？
...and force him down the aisle, okay?
我已经可以预见到 "麦克 你愿意娶菲比吗？"
I can just see it. "Mike, do you take Phoebe?"
你知道吗？那真是每个女孩的梦想
You know? It's every girl's dream.
你真的认为 嫁给别人就可以解决？
Do you really think marrying someone else is the right answer?
当然 听着 最重要的是 我爱麦克…大卫
Sure. Look, okay, bottom line? I love Mike... David!
大卫 我爱大卫
David! I love David.
别那样看我 戴安娜罗丝
Don't look at me that way, Roseanne Roseannadanna.
"藉由电脑断层扫描跟电脑成像 我们可以用非常逼真的方式…
"By using CT scans and computer imaging, we can, in a very real way...
将中生代时期带到二十一世纪"
bring the Mesozoic Era into the 21st century."
太棒了
It's great.
你会成为此次研讨会的明星
You'll be the hit of the conference.
你知道吗？明天还会更好
It'll be even better tomorrow...
因为我不会一直被乔伊打断…
because I won't be constantly interrupted by Joey...
他一直来检查我枕头上 放了巧克力没有
checking to see if they put chocolates on my pillow yet.
- 大家好   - 巧克力还没送来
- Hey, guys.     - The chocolates aren't here.
该死
Damn it!
罗斯刚念完他的演讲稿给我听 真是精彩
Ross just read me his speech. It's fantastic.
在电脑里面吗？因为我也想看
Oh, is it on the computer? Because I'd love to give it a read.
如果你想要查电子邮件就说吧
If you want to check your e-mail, just ask.
什么？我可以吗？
What? May I?
这雨是怎么回事 盖勒？我报名参加恐龙营的时候…
What's with the rain, Geller? I mean, when I signed up for dino week...
没有人说过现在是雨季
nobody said anything about it being monsoon season.
- 雨季其实是六月到十二月   - 现在不是时候 查莉
- The wet season is June to December.     - It's not the time, Charlie.
哎呀 糟糕 天哪 不会吧
Oh, no. No, no! Dear God, no!
怎么了？有人比你抢先标下茶壶吗？
What, did someone outbid you for the teapot?
秘密茶壶
Secret teapot.
你的电脑 我不知道怎么… 全部消失了
Your computer. I don't know what... Everything's gone.
- 什么意思？ - 定是病毒
- What do you mean?      - Must be a virus.
我想它把你的硬碟全杀掉了
I think it erased your hard drive.
什么？我的天啊 你干了什么好事？
What? Oh, my God. What did you do?
一个我不认识的人寄信给我 然后我打开了
Someone I don't know sent me an e-mail and I opened it.
- 为什么？你为何要打开？ - 那又没有写"这是病毒“!
- Why? Why would you open it?     - Well, it didn't say, "This is a virus."
- 那上面写什么？ - "裸体的…"
- What did it say?     - "Nude..."
"安娜库妮可娃的照片"
"Pictures of Anna Kournikova."
- 我很抱歉   - 那我怎么办？
- I'm so sorry.     - What am I gonna do?
- 钱德 我的演讲稿不见了   - 没有不见
- My speech is gone!     - It's not gone.
我相信你有列印出来 你有印出来吧？
I'm sure you printed out a copy. You have a hard copy?
不 我没有
No, I don't!
那你现在一定很气自己
Well, you must be pretty mad at yourself right now.
- 真的不见了吗？ - 不见了
- It's really gone?     - Yep.
我想要谢谢你们来这里…
I'd like to thank you guys for coming down here...
抱怨雨 而且毁了我的事业前途
to complain about the rain and ruin my career.
- 我觉得非常抱歉   - 你是应该要抱歉
- I just feel awful.     - Yeah, you should.
安娜库妮可娃的裸照？她根本什么大赛都没赢过
Nude pictures of Anna Kournikova? She's never even won a major tournament.
我有试过比莉珍金 但是…
Well, I tried Billie Jean King, but...
你知道吗？你跟摩妮卡 那种我要杀了你的表情一模一样
You know, you and Monica have the same I'm-gonna-kill-you look.
我通常亲她一下 就可以逃过一劫
I can usually make it go away by kissing her.
滚出去
Get out.
我工作的电脑也常常发生这种事
You know, this happens all the time to my computer at work.
- 那你怎么办？ - 我通常会…
- What do you do?     - I usually go...
到别人的电脑上 玩俄罗斯方块
play Tetris on somebody else's computer.
我不敢相信会发生这种事
I can't believe this is happening.
我明天就要演讲了
I have to give the keynote speech tomorrow.
我要站在所有人面前 我要说什么呢？
I have to stand up in front of all these people. What am I gonna say?
你可以用我背下来 参加试镜的那段话
You can use a speech I memorized for auditions.
我认为你在《星际大战》里的独白 不会对我有帮助 乔伊
I don't think your monologue from Star Wars is gonna help me right now.
罗斯 我们可以一起解决问题 我听过你的演讲
Ross, we can solve this. I just heard your speech.
我们可以重建 我们有一整晚的时间
We can re-create it. We've got all night.
怎么？你真的认为我们办得到？
What, you really think we can do that?
等等 乔伊跟我已经约好 一起去吃晚餐
Oh, wait. Joey and I are supposed to have dinner.
别担心 我知道罗斯需要你
Don't worry about that. I mean, Ross needs you.
瑞秋跟我会留下来尽量帮忙
Rachel and I will stay and help any way we can.
好吧 我们现在就开始
All right. Okay, let's do it.
我知道我们一开始 是讨论碳年代测定法的缺点
Well, I know we start by discussing the shortcomings of carbon dating.
我接着解说 什么事件显然…
And then I move on to what is clearly the defining moment...
是中生代的关键时刻 原始大陆的分裂 不是吗？
of the Mesozoic Era, the breakup of Pangaea. Hello?
再来是三叠纪的概观
And then there's the overview of the Triassic.
这一切有没有可能 是在很遥远的银河系发生的？
Ooh, ooh. Any chance any of this happened in a galaxy far, far away?
- 喂？ - 好了 麦克？
- Hello?     - Okay, Mike?
闹够了 你爱菲比 而她也爱你
Enough is enough. You love Phoebe, and she loves you.
所以不要再说什么 "我不想结婚"的话了
So get over your I-never-wanna-get-married thing...
赶快站出来
and step up!
你是谁？
Who is this?
我是摩妮卡 菲比的朋友
This is Monica, Phoebe's friend.
听着 菲比跟大卫复合了
Listen. Phoebe is back with David.
他即将要求婚 而她会答应
He's gonna propose, and she's gonna say yes...
但是我知道 她真正想要的是跟你在一起
but I know she really wants to be with you.
他要求婚了？
He's gonna propose?
对不起 你说什么？该死的头发遮住我听不到
I'm sorry, did you say something? I can't hear through all this damned hair!
如果菲比想要嫁给大卫 那就去吧
If Phoebe wants to marry David, she should.
我不会从中作梗 你也不应该
I'm not gonna stand in the way of that. Neither should you.
不用你来告诉我该怎么做 是我来告诉你怎么做
You don't tell me what to do. I tell you what to do.
打电话给她 她在巴贝多的天堂饭店
Just call her. She's at the Paradise Hotel in Barbados.
对了 你也有卷发
And while I've got you, you've got curly hair.
在湿气重的地方你怎么办？
What do you do in the humidity?
该死
Damn it!
- 嗯 我希望你很快乐   - 我也希望你很快乐 老婆
- Well, I hope you're happy.     - Aw, I hope you're happy too, honey.
菲比会答应大卫的求婚
Phoebe's going to say yes to David.
- 这就是你爱管闲事的结果   - 菲比要答应？太棒了
- That's what happens when you meddle.     - Phoebe's gonna say yes? That's great.
不 一点也不棒 她还爱着麦克
No, it's not. She's still in love with Mike.
- 那不会有什么结果吗？ - 不会 我已经打过电话了
- There's no chance that will work?     - No, I called.
- 不会有结果   - 鸡婆 鸡婆
- It's not gonna happen.     - Meddler! Meddler!
如果不是你先多管闲事…
If you hadn't meddled to start with...
我就不用插手进来管事了
then I wouldn't have had to go in and meddle myself.
不管我们怎么插手 都没有办法补救…
No matter how much we meddle, we'll never be able to unmeddle...
你一开始多管闲事惹出来的祸
the thing that you meddled up in the first place!
这场假期真是烂
This vacation sucks!
(欢迎古生物学家们)
- 我好无聊   - 嗯
- I'm so bored.     - Mm.
该死的雨 我们什么事都做不了
Stupid rain. We can't do anything.
我带了一些书来 我们可以看点书
Well, I brought some books. We could read.
嘿 还没糟糕到那个地步
Hey, it hasn't come to that yet.
嘿 等一下 不好意思
Hey, hey, hey, don't mind if I do.
对不起 先生 这是给药学研讨会的
I'm sorry, sir, these are for the pharmaceutical convention.
瑞秋 你想要去参加研讨会吗？
You feel like going to a convention?
- 我们不行 我们不是药剂师   - 我知道我们不是…
- We can't. We're not pharmacists.     - I know we're not...
但是法兰克马迭欧跟伊娃齐罗欧…
but Frank Madaio and Eva...
- 凯特米勒   - 凯特米勒就对了
- Kate Miller.     - Kate Miller it is.
- 好的   - 喔 很好…
- Okay.     - Oh, good...
这是这个周末 我最接近性爱的时刻了
And that's the most sex I'm gonna have this weekend.
如果是这样 我应该要确定这黏得够牢罗？
Well, in that case, should I make sure it's on real good?
- 谢谢你   - 不客气
- Thank you.     - you're welcome
喔 然后你开始谈 将中生代世纪…
Oh, and then you said that thing about bringing the Mesozoic Era...
带到二十一世纪
into the 21st century.
对喔 就这样吗？
Well, yeah. That's it?
- 是的   - 天啊 我们办到了
- Yeah.     - Oh, my God. We did it.
事实上是我办到了 罗斯 演讲稿是你的 你记得的却少得惊人
Actually, I did it, Ross. You remembered shockingly little of your own speech.
是的 但是我用沐浴产品 做了个金字塔
Yes, but I did make a pyramid out of the bath products.
真是佩服 谢谢你 真的很谢谢你
Oh, this is amazing. Thank you. Thank you so much.
这项链真漂亮
That's a pretty necklace.
谢谢
Thank you.
我们庆祝一下吧？要来点香槟吗？
Hey, what do you say we celebrate? Champagne?
好啊 软木塞留着 我们可以把瓶子装满水…
Yeah! Save the cork, and that way, we can fill the bottle with water...
然后再放回去 这样他们就不会收钱了
and put it back so they don't charge you.
我的天啊 我爱你
Oh, my God, I love you.
艾玛这张照片真是可爱 而这是你儿子…
This is such a cute picture of Emma. And is this your son...
还是某个你渡假时 会带在身上的小男孩照片？
or just some kid whose picture you bring on vacation?
那是班 我第一次婚姻生的儿子
That's Ben, my son from my first marriage.
- 你第一次婚姻？ - 是的
- Your first marriage?     - Yeah.
你结过不只一次婚吗？
You've been married more than once?
没有
No.
嗯
Mm.
那你为什么离婚呢？
So why'd you break up?
嗯 因为…
Oh, it was...
很复杂 她是…
It's complicated, you know? She was, uh...
同性恋
guy.
我的天啊
Oh, my God.
这实在太酷了
This is so cool!
为这种事兴奋是很奇怪的事
Okay. Odd thing to get excited about.
不是 只是我曾经订过婚 而那梱男的竟然是同志
No, it's just that I was engaged to a guy who turned out to be gay.
嘿 击掌吧
Hey! High-five!
你不觉得没有看出瑞倪 实在是很笨？
Didn't you feel so stupid that you didn't see the signs?
我未婚夫总是跟 他的"网球球友"一起度周末
My fiancé was always going on long weekends with his "tennis partner."
我老婆有一年跟一个朋友 天天都到健身房报到
My wife had a workout friend she went to the gym with every day for a year.
她也没有变结实
She didn't get any fitter.
- 每个人都说"我早就知道了"   - 对嘛
- Everybody's like, "I knew all along."     - I know.
如果你们知道 怎么不告诉我？打个电话 留个字条什么的
If you knew, why didn't you tell me? I mean, call, leave a note.
"嗨 只是过来告诉你 你老婆是同性恋"
"Hi. Just dropped by to say your wife's gay."
- 对嘛   - 然后…
- I know.     - And then...
然后你试着把危机变转机…
And then you try to make the best of a bad situation...
所以提出三人行的建议
so you float the idea of a threesome.
我没有那样做
I didn't do that.
我也没有
Me neither.
谁想得到药剂师们会这么好玩
Well, who knew? Pharmacists are fun.
对啊 那位老太太 最后都已经准备要带你回家了
I know. That old lady at the end was ready to take you home.
全世界的药都还不够 瑞秋
Not enough pills in the world, Rach.
那你呢？你才是单身的人 有没有看到喜欢的？
What about you, huh? You're the single one. See anybody in there you like?
让我想想 那梱跟我 说过话的大个儿…
Well, let's see. There was that really big guy that I was talking to...
他的胸部很不错
with the really nice breasts.
那在家乡呢？
But what about back home?
有什么吗？你有喜欢的人吗？
Anything going on there? Anybody you like?
没有
No.
- 有的 你脸红了   - 没有 我才没有脸红
- There is. You're blushing.     - No, I'm not blushing...
这是晒伤的…
and I'm sunburned.
因为下雨的缘故
From, you know, the rain.
你有喜欢的人 告诉我是谁
You like someone. Tell me who.
- 告诉我是谁 说啦   - 不 乔伊
- Tell me who it is. Come on.     - No. Joey.
你喜欢谁啊？别想轻易躲掉
Who do you like? You're not getting away that easy.
- 你喜欢谁？ - 乔伊 别这样
- Who do you like?     - Joey, come on!
没什么大不了的 你知道吗？又不是说会发生什么事
It doesn't matter, you know? It's not like anything's gonna happen.
什么？为什么不会？瑞秋 有谁是你得不到的？
What? Why not? Rach, who can you not get?
好 你真想知道是谁吗？
Okay. Okay. You really want to know who it is?
- 很想 是谁？ - 你真的想？
- Yeah. Who is it?     - Do you?
- 对   - 嗨
- Yeah.     - Hey.
- 嗨   - 我才刚留言给你
- Hey.     - I just left you a message.
罗斯跟我本来要去吃点东西…
Ross and I were gonna go grab a bite...
但是既然你在这里 我们可以一起去吃晚餐了
but now that you're here, we could have that dinner.
没错 当然 演讲稿写完了吗？
Right! Of course. Hey, did you guys finish the speech?
完成了 我们完成了 非常谢谢你
Yep! We got it. We got it. Thank you so much.
- 我做得很开心   - 是啊
- I had a great time.     - Yeah.
这还没完 因为我真的想知道…
This isn't over, because I really want to know...
等一下 等一下
Later. Later.
- 那我们走吧？ - 好的
- So shall we?     - Yeah.
- 好的   - 晚安
- Okay.     - Good night.
晚安
Good night.
- 好吧 晚安   - 晚安 罗斯
- Okay, good night.     - Good night, Ross.
我不敢相信她要答应
I can't believe she's gonna say yes to David.
她显然还爱着麦克
She's clearly in love with Mike.
你这样子 实在很难把你的话当真
You know, it's very hard to take you seriously when you look like that.
菲比 我有一些话要说
Um... Phoebe, um, I have, uh, something I want to say.
天啊 他要开口了 我看不下去 我们走吧
Oh, God, he's gonna do it. I cannot watch this. Let's go.
我想我们还有时间 你有听过他说话吗？
I think we have time. Have you heard him talk?
"菲比 我将会很荣幸如果…" 说快点 大卫
"Uh, Phoebe, um, I would be honored if, uh, uh..." Spit it out, David!
菲比…
Uh, Phoebe, um...
你实在是太迷人了 我们分开的那段日子非常难熬
You're an amazing woman, and the time we spent apart was unbearable.
当然明斯克卫生设施员工罢工 让情况更糟
Of course, the sanitation strikes in Minsk didn't help.
当然 好的 然后呢？
Sure. Okay. Yeah.
但是现在我们又在一起了 我再也不想跟你分开
But, um, well, now that we're together again, I don't ever want to be apart.
所以…
So to that end...
- 喔 我的天啊 麦克   - 事实上 我是大卫
- Oh, my God, Mike.     - It's David, actually.
麦克在这里 不
No, Mike's here.
麦克 嘿
Oh, hey, Mike.
嗨 大卫
Hi, David.
钱德 摩妮…哇
Chandler. Monic... Oh!
是湿气
It's the humidity!
- 嗨 菲比   - 你在这里做什么？
- Hi, Phoebe.     - What are you doing here?
我有个问题一定要问你
I have a question I need to ask you.
我也有问题要问她
I have a question I was kind of gonna ask her myself.
我了解 但是你问之前 她真的需要先听我说
Yeah, I understand, but before you do, she really needs to hear this.
好吧
Okay.
- 那我的座位你也想要坐喽？ - 噢 那就谢谢你了
- Would you care for my seat as well?     - Actually, yeah, that'd be great.
很公平 你大老远赶来
Well, that's fair, you've had a long trip.
菲比 我爱你
Phoebe, I love you.
我过去这几个月非常想念你
I've missed you so much these last few months.
我原本以为 导致我们分手的是个好理由
I thought we were apart for a good reason...
但是我发现 根本没有理由好到…
but I realized that there was no reason good enough...
让我决定不和你共度下半辈子
to keep me from spending the rest of my life with you.
这有点毁了 我本来打算要说的话
Kind of steps on the toes of what I was going to say.
抱歉 大卫 但是她真的需要知道
I'm sorry, David, but she really has to know this.
好吧 但是之后 我要在外面跟你单挑
All right, but after this, I want to see you outside.
如果外面雨停了的话
If the rain stops.
你是我遇过最不可思议的女人
You're the most incredible woman I've ever met.
我怎么能够失去你？我现在身上没有戒指
How could I lose you? Now, I don't actually have a ring.
- 我有戒指   - 我不会在这时候炫耀 老兄
- I have a ring.     - I wouldn't brag about that, big guy.
但是 菲比…
But, Phoebe...
你愿意嫁给我吗？
will you marry me?
不
No.
哈哈
Ha-ha.
我爱你 但是我从来不需要你求婚
I love you, but I never needed a proposal from you.
我只需要知道 我们之间可以有发展
I just needed to know we were headed somewhere.
- 我们是有未来的   - 我们可以有任何你想要的未来
- That we had a future.     - We can have any future you want.
好 我要走了
Okay, well, I'm gonna take off.
大卫 我很抱歉 真对不起
David, I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
让我知道一下 如果我先问了…
Just so I know, if I had asked first?
我有可能会答应 但那是不对的
Yeah, I might have said yes, but that would've been wrong.
你不用解释 没关系
Please, you don't have to explain.
如果我当初没有去明斯克…
I mean, perhaps if I hadn't gone to Minsk...
我们之间可能就没问题了 而我也不会毁了我的事业
things would have worked out for us, and I wouldn't have ruined my career.
或是因冻疮而失去那只脚趾
Or lost that toe to frostbite.
那是趟好旅程
It was a good trip.
- 我现在可以拥抱你吗？ - 喔 可以
- Is it okay if I hug you now?     - Oh, yes.
就是因为我们多管闲事 知道吗？
Because of our meddling! All right?
很舒服吧？如此安静 我可以整天都躺在这里
Oh, isn't this nice? It's so quiet. I could just lie here all day.
是啊
Oh, I know.
- 打开窗帘 打开窗帘   - 真高兴我们的房间是相通的
- Open your drapes! Open your drapes!     - So glad we got adjoining rooms.
- 太阳出来了   - 嘿 记得我还有眼角膜的时候吗？
- The sun is out!     - Hey! Remember when I had corneas?
赶快去游泳池占位子
Go to the pool and reserve chairs.
我会拿杂志跟防晒乳液
I will get the magazines and the lotion.
罗斯的演讲再四十五分钟就开始了
Ladies? Ross' speech is in 45 minutes.
- 不会吧   - 该死
- No!     - Damn it!
墙壁很薄的 你们这些人
Walls are pretty thin, guys.
"我们必须考量最近核磁共振与去气核醣核酸测试的资料…
"Then we have to weigh the data from recent MRI scans and DNA testing...
对多年来通过碳年代测定 收集资料的方式形成了一些疑点
which call into question information gathered from years of carbon dating."
瞧瞧那个坐在游泳池畔 晒太阳的女人
Look at the woman sitting out by the pool getting tan.
她的皮都变粗生皱纹了 我真是嫉妒
She's all leathery and wrinkled. I'm so jealous!
最后 再加上 最近发现的大量新物种
"Finally, factor in the profusion of new species recently discovered.
巨兽龙
Giganotosaurus.
- 阿根廷龙   - 更不用提冷龙(音似唇泡疹)
- Argentinosaurus."     - Not to mention Coldsaurus.
"而这些只是草食性的 我还没有要提到肉食性··
"And that's just the herbivores. I'm not even gonna discuss the carnivores.
他们都已经有大头症了
Their heads are already too big.
蛮讽刺的 因为他们大脑发育不良"
Which is ironic, considering their stunted cerebral development."
真的吗？
Really?
"但是撇开玩笑不谈 这近似于…
"But all kidding aside, in much the same way...
匠人现在被认为 与直立人(音近勃起)不同种"
that Homo ergaster is thought to be a separate species from Homo erectus..."
- 什么？ - 他说"直立人"
- What?     - He said "erectus."
- 你在开玩笑吗？ - 不 他是真的那样说
- You're kidding, right?     - No, he really said it.
"虽然介于这些中生代化石…
"And while there are certainly vast differences...
跟直立人例子之间 有许多巨大的差异"
between these Mesozoic fossils and the example of Homo erectus..."
勃起？
Erectus?
- 同性恋   - 没错
- Homo.     - Right.
"以非常逼真的方式 我们可以将中生代时期带到二十一世纪"
"In a very real way, we can bring the Mesozoic Era into the 21 st century."
谢谢大家
Thank you.
- 真的很棒   - 谢谢你们
- Really great.     - Thanks, guys.
我认为那很精采
I thought it was wonderful.
我是康乃尔大学的 杰维斯欧伯劳
Jarvis Oberblau. Cornell.
你突显出来的议题 尤其是你这样年轻而且…
I mean, the ideas you put forth, and from someone so young and...
现在我们只是握着手
Okay, now we're just holding hands.
好 我们要去海滩了 演讲真的很棒
Alrighty. We're gonna hit the beach. That was really great.
- 谢谢   - 是啊 而且很好笑
- Oh, thank you.     - Yeah. Oh, and so funny.
- 别太累   - 好的 谢谢 非常谢谢
- Take it easy.     - All right, thanks. Thanks so much.
我无法形容 你们在这里对我的意义有多重大
I can't tell you how much it means that you were here.
你在开玩笑吗？我们不可能会错过的
You kidding? We wouldn't have missed it.
噢
Oh.
我回来了
I'm back.
好 失陪一下
Okay. Well, excuse me?
嘿
Hey.
- 怎么样？ - 你真是了不起
- Well?     - You were incredible.
你完全迷住他们了
You blew them away.
我无法形容 在人群中看到你的脸感觉有多棒
I can't tell you how great it was to look in the crowd and see your face.
你知道你嘴巴在跟着我念吗？
I mean, did you know you were mouthing the words along with me?
- 我才没有   - 不 没关系
- I was not.     - No, it's okay.
那让我自觉像个摇滚巨星
It made me feel like a rock star.
我的天啊 我居然是个追星大粉丝
Oh, my God. I'm your groupie.
你最好不要脱光光 躲在我的房间里喔
Hey, I better not find you naked in my hotel room.
哎呀 我扯太远了
Look, I took it too far.
不敢相信又在下雨了 真是不公平
I can't believe it's raining again. It's so unfair.
往好处想就是我们不用看到…
Well, on the bright side, now we won't have to see...
那些古生物学家脱掉上衣
all these paleontologists with their shirts off.
不是你们
Not you guys.
你们还不错
You've got it going on.
- 我们今天要做什么？ - 他们楼下有游戏间
- What will we do today?     - They have a game room downstairs.
有兵乓球和其他的东西
They have Ping-Pong and stuff.
乒乓球？亲爱的 他们有乒乓球耶
Ping-Pong? Honey, they have Ping-Pong.
- 我们来玩   - 我不要
- Let's play.     - I don't think so.
- 为什么不要？ - 你知道你得失心很重
- Why not?     - You know how competitive you get.
我可以说那样很可爱 但别人都不同意 而且我是在说谎
And while I say it's cute, others disagree, and I'm lying.
- 我又不是- 直都那样糟糕   - 是吗？
- I'm not always that bad.     - Oh, yeah?
我们上次玩的时候 发生什么事？
What happened when we played last time?
我揍了你
I punched you.
- 还有呢？ - 还有菲比
- And?     - Phoebe.
- 还有呢？ - 我把你们的头撞在一起
- And?     - I clunked your heads together.
- 你在这里   - 嘿 听着
- There you are.     - Hey. Listen.
只要雨一停 我们一定要去浮潜
As soon as it stops raining, we have got to go snorkeling.
有个小孩告诉我有海龟 如果你对着他的脸吹泡泡…
Some kid told me about this sea turtle. If you blow bubbles in his face...
他会追着你跑喔
he chases you.
很抱歉 我不能去 我整个下午都要主持小组讨论
I'm sorry, I can't. I'm running a discussion group all afternoon.
噢
Oh.
没关系 我找别人去好了
That's okay. I'll find someone else to do it.
我是可以一个人去 但是…
I'd do it alone, but, uh...
不知道海龟 如果抓到我会发生什么事
I don't know what happens if the sea turtle catches you.
我觉得很不好意思
You know, I feel so bad.
我整趟旅途都没有跟你在一起 尤其是昨晚…
I haven't seen you this whole trip. Especially last night...
不用担心 没关系 我跟瑞秋玩得很开心
Don't worry about it. It was fine. I had the best time with Rachel.
我只是为你难过 跟罗斯关在房间里赶演讲稿
I just felt bad for you, stuck in that room working on Ross' speech.
事实上 结果还蛮好玩的
Actually, it turned out to be a lot of fun.
那至少我们都过得很愉快 不是吗？
Oh, well, at least we're both having fun, right?
- 我们不在一起却很快乐 很怪吧？ - 是啊
- Is it weird that it's not with each other?     - Yeah.
有一点 是啊
A little bit, yeah.
我想我们需要谈谈
I think we need to talk.
是啊 我想我们是需要
Yeah, I think we do.
谈什么呢？
About what?
- 别这样 会很好玩的啦   - 好吧
- Come on, you guys, it'll be fun!     - All right.
- 不计分我才要玩   - 那我们怎么知道谁赢呢？
- I'll play if we don't keep score.     - Well, then how do we know who wins?
- 没有人会赢   - 所以我们是四个输家 太好了
- Nobody wins.     - So we're just four losers. Super.
- 我不要跟她玩   - 我不玩了
- Well, I'm not playing with her.     - I'm out.
- 我跟你玩   - 好的
- I'll play you.     - Okay.
- 麦克 你不知道你在做什么   - 她会很疯狂的
- You don't know what you're doing.     - She gets crazy.
这个疤痕是从画图猜字游戏来的
This scar? That's from Pictionary.
我想我会没事的
I think I'll be all right.
- 你想要先热身一下吗？ - 当然 如果你想要的话
- You want to volley a bit for serve?     - Sure, if you want to.
嚯
Ho!
对了 我很厉害
Oh, by the way, I'm awesome.
天哪 这两个人一模一样
Oh, dear God, there's two of them.
- 你准备好要上场了吗？ - 当然
- You ready to play?     - Hell, yeah.
- 你有看过他这一面吗？ - 没有 我以为他跟你一样软弱
- Did you know this about him?     - No idea. I thought he was soft like you.
- 想要更刺激点吗？ - 你想赌多少？
- Want to make it more interesting?     - How much you thinking?
- 十块钱一局？ - 加到五十块钱好了
- Ten bucks a game?     - Make it 50.
- 我加到一百块钱   －一千…
- I'll make it 100.     - One thousand...
好了
Okay!
我们掷铜板来决定谁先开球 你有铜板吗？
We'll flip to see who goes first. You got a quarter?
没有 你们两个女生谁有铜板？
No. Either of you girls got a quarter?
亲爱的 这种骂人的话 都用到他身上
Honey, try to focus the trash talk on him.
- 摩妮卡 你来猜   - 正面 不 背面 正面
- Monica, you call it.     - Heads. No, tails! Heads!
- 背面   - 机率有这样低吗？
- Tails.     - Oh, what are the chances?
- 我得分   - 不 我可不这么认为
- Hah! My point!     - Oh, no, I don't think so.
根据桌球标准规则 若参赛者 在任何时间将没握球拍的手…
Standard rules: If at any time a player uses his nonracket-bearing hand...
碰触到球桌表面 得分不算
to touch the playing surface, he or she forfeits the point.
他曾经是律师
He was a lawyer.
东岸的天气十分良好
All the East Coast is having beautiful weather.
纽约摄氏二十二度 而且阳光普照
In New York, it's 72 and sunny.
气象婊子
Oh. Weather bitch.
门没锁
It's open.
- 嗨 乔伊   - 嘿
- Hi, Joe.     - Hey.
- 怎么了？还好吗？ - 查莉跟我分手了
- What? Is everything okay?     - Charlie and I broke up.
不会吧 为什么？
No. Why?
嗯 她说我们没有任何共同点
Well, she said we have nothing in common.
这真是胡说
That's crazy.
不 是真的 我们没有任何共同点
No, it's not. We have nothing in common.
- 是啊 是没错   - 是啊
- Yeah, that's true.     - Yeah.
她应该跟罗斯那样的人在一起
I mean, she should be with someone more like Ross.
你知道 他也会用那些很艰深的字眼
You know, I mean he uses all those big words too.
- 天啊 聪明的人真是无趣   - 嗯 喂
- Man, smart people are dull.     - Well, hey!
好了 瑞秋
Okay, Rach.
我觉得好蠢 你知道吗？我为什么一直喜欢不适合我的女生呢？
I feel so stupid, you know? Why do I keep going after the wrong girls?
- 你在说什么？ - 喔 少来了
- What are you talking about?     - Oh, come on.
先是你 然后是查莉 这就像是…我到底是哪根筋不对？
I mean, there's you, then there's Charlie. It's like... What the hell's my problem?
我只是…
I just...
好吧 或许你并没有都跟 不适合你的女生在一起
Okay. Maybe you're not always going after the wrong girl.
我告诉你 瑞秋 查莉并不适合我
I'm telling you, Rach, Charlie is not right for me.
- 我不是在说她   - 是喔 那谁呢？
- I'm not talking about her.     - Well, then, who?
我上个月约过的那个女服务生吗？
The waitress I went out with last month?
- 你知道吗？算了   - 不…
- You know what? Forget it.     - No, no, no, no.
- 你是在说谁呢？ - 不 我不…
- Who are you talking about?     - No, I don't...
事实上我也不知道 我在说什么 所以…
I actually don't know who I'm talking about, so...
- 好吧   - 嗯
- Okay.     - Yeah.
我要去看看今晚有没有办法 订到另一间房间
Well, I'm gonna go see if I can get a room for tonight.
- 待会儿见   - 好啊
- And I'll see you later.     - Yeah, sure. Okay.
- 你喜欢我？ - 呃
- You like me?     - Okay.
- 我们不要过度强调这件事   - 这是一件大事
- Let's not make a big thing about this.     - It's a huge thing!
你很不合作喔 乔伊
Okay, not working with me, Joe.
听着 事情是这样的 最近 我有些想法
Look, here's the thing. Lately, I have been having thoughts.
应该说是冥想
Musings, if you will.
- 多久了？ - 大概只有一个月
- Well, for how long?     - Oh, only like a month.
－一个月   - 嗯…
- A month?!     - Well...
小声点 或许只是一些疯狂的想法 但是有时候我就是会想啊
Dial it down. Listen, maybe they're crazy thoughts, but sometimes I do.
我一直在想我们之间的可能性
I have been thinking about, you know, us.
- 好 现在音调可以提高一点   - 你说的对 好吧
- Okay, dial it up a little.     - Oh, you're right. Okay.
- 我只有一个问题   - 说吧
- I just have a question.     - Shoot.
- 你到底是在搞什么？ - 我也不是想做什么
- What the hell are you doing?     - I'm not trying to do anything.
只是我们在一起时都非常开心 你知道吗？
It's just, we have such a good time when we're together, you know?
你难道都没有好奇过 那会是怎样的情形吗？
And I mean, aren't you just a little curious what it would be like?
我好奇过吗？我就跟…
Am I curious? I mean, I'm as curious as...
乔治一样好奇
George!
谁？
Who?
- 好奇乔治啊   - 噢
- Curious George!     - Oh!
那只猴子 还有那个戴黄帽的男人
You know, the monkey and the guy with the yellow hat.
- 我当然记得   - 他还有自己的送报路线
- Of course. I remember.     - He had a paper route.
是啊 没错
Yeah, he did.
- 你看 这就是我在说的   - 对 我们在一起太好玩了
- See, this is what I'm talking about.     - No, I know. We're great!
但是瑞秋 不 不能这样
But, Rach, no, this can't happen.
不能有一点点机会吗？
Can't it just happen a little bit?
- 不 一点也不行   - 为什么不行？
- No! It can't happen at all!     - Why not?
我也非常想要 好吗？
Because, look, no one wants this to happen more than me, okay?
我在脑海中已经幻想过 这情节一百次了
I have gone over this moment in my head 100 times...
而且我从没拒绝过
and not once did I ever say no.
我不能这样对待罗斯
I couldn't do it to Ross.
- 但之前你却不是这样   - 我知道…
- But that wasn't gonna stop you before.     - I know. I know...
但是在那之后我想了很多 这是不对的
but I've thought about it a lot since then, and it just wouldn't be right.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
我也很抱歉
I'm sorry too.
天啊 我不应该说出来的
Oh, God, I shouldn't have said anything.
不…别这样 我们没事的
No, no, no, no. Hey, we'll be fine.
- 就像你所说的 这没有什么   - 没错
- Like you said, it's no big deal.     - It's not a big deal.
- 没有什么   - 真的是没有什么
- No big deal.     - It's so not a big deal.
- 待会儿见 好   - 好的 太好了
- I'll see you later. All right, hey.     - Okay, great.
好…
Okay... Oh!
真抱歉喔 我想… 我想那可能没有去到桌面
Oh, I'm sorry, I think... I think that may have missed the table.
- 是吗？ - 是的
- Oh, do you?     - Yeah.
- Do you?     - Yeah.
- 是吗？ - 是的
- Do you?     - Yeah!
- 你真的认为他这样很有魅力？ - 当然
- You really find this attractive on him?     - Oh, yeah.
你是在说 你现在没有 被摩妮卡撩得心痒痒的吗？
Are you telling me you're not even a little turned on by Monica right now?
这是婚后我第一次觉得 我是比较有魅力的那一个
This is the first time in our marriage that I've felt like the more attractive one.
加油 麦克 你可以打败她的
All right, come on, Mike. You can beat her.
把她打得落花流水
Knock that dog off her head.
- 该死   - 我跟他上床喔
- Oh, damn it!     - I sleep with him!
- 关键分数   - 别太骄傲
- Game point.     - Don't get too cocky.
记住上次是我赢的
Remember, I won the last one.
喔 对了 输给一个女生感觉如何？
Oh, by the way, how did that feel, losing to a girl?
你应该先照照镜子再说
You should look in the mirror before you call yourself that.
- 不 不 不   - 而这就是这样结束的
- No! No! No!     - And that's how it's done.
好了
Okey-dokey.
你们都各赢一局 而我感觉我的寿命好像短了一年
You've each won a game, and I've lost what's felt like a year of my life.
每个人都可以跟一个赢家回家
Everybody goes home a winner.
- 三战两胜？ - 我就是这样想
- Best of three?     - What I'm thinking.
我应该运用我的隐形术 来打击犯罪或是做坏事？
Should I use my invisibility to fight crime or for evil?
- 开球吧 木头人   - "开球吧 木头人"
- Serve the ball, chump.     - "Serve the ball, chump."
好 重披战袍会更好 麦克 重披战袍会更好
Okay, better comebacks, Mike. Better comebacks.
我是说说而已 我在 阿迪朗达克山区有间小木屋
I'm just saying, I have a cabin in the Adirondacks.
如果你想要远离尘嚣 那就…
If you ever want to get away from the city, well, that'd be...
太美妙了
just nifty.
嗯 我现在事情是蛮多的
Well, I've kind of got a lot on my plate right now.
不是说我不喜欢 跟陌生男人到乡间度周末
Not that I wouldn't love a weekend in the country with a strange man.
- 杰维斯？ - 喔 你回来了
- Jarvis?     - Oh, you're back.
- 这是我老婆 南西   - 少来了
- This is my wife, Nancy.     - Well, get out!
罗斯 我可以跟你谈谈吗？
Ross? Can I talk to you for a minute?
当然了
Yes, please.
怎么了？
So, what's going on?
嗯 乔伊跟我分手了
Well, Joey and I broke up.
- 我的天啊 发生了什么事？ - 乔伊是个好男人…
- Oh, my God. What happened?     - Joey is a great guy...
但是我们就是… 我们很不一样
but we're just... We're so different.
像是在你演讲的时候 他一直在笑"直立人"
I mean, like, during your speech, he kept laughing at "Homo erectus."
我就知道是他
I knew that was him!
反正 我只是… 我想这样是最好的
Anyway, I just... I think it's for the best.
- 嘿 你还好吗？ - 还好
- Hey. Hey, you okay?     - I guess.
还有…
There was...
我跟乔伊分手 还有另外一个原因
There was another reason that I thought it was time to end it with Joey.
我开始发觉 我对另外一个人有感觉
I started to realize that I was having feelings for someone else.
好的 盖勒 研讨会的最后一天了
Okay, Geller. Last day of the conference.
你知道主讲人会被怎么样
You know what happens to the keynote speaker.
克雷克教授 我们正在谈话
Professor Klarik, we're in the middle of a conversation here.
不能等会儿再丢他进游泳池吗？
Can't you throw him in the pool later?
不然就是把你们两个都丢进去
Or we could throw you both in now.
各位先生 拜托 我们会不会太老了？
Okay, gentlemen, please. Aren't we a little old for this?
我是说我们是科学家 好吗？我们都有学术素养
I mean, we're scientists, all right? We're academics...
而且最重要的是 你们必须要先捉到我们
and most importantly you will have to catch us first.
跑 跑 跑
Go! Go! Go!
好 又平手了 四十一比四十一
Okay, so it's tied again, 41 to 41.
- 好 你们给我听着 够了   - 不
- Okay, look, enough is enough. MONICA: No.
我只要再两分就可以打败他了
I just have two more points to beat him.
摩妮卡 一小时前你就这样说了
Monica, that was also true an hour ago!
拜托 瞧瞧你自己
I mean, please, look at you.
你的手都起水泡了 你连站都站不住 你的头发整个莫名奇妙
Your hand is blistered, you can barely stand, your hair is inexplicable!
你已经证明你跟他一样厉害
You've already proven you're just as good as he is.
我们已经错过晚餐预约 所以我们就上楼去…
We missed our dinner reservation, let's go upstairs...
点客房服务 洗个澡 然后剃光你的头发
order room service, take a shower and shave your head!
我不能这样走掉 我已经投入四个小时了
I can't just walk away. I've put in four hours.
你娶我的时候 你就知道我是这样
You knew this about me when you married me.
你答应无论我生病 或是健康都要照顾我的
You agreed to take me in sickness and in health.
这就是我的病
Well, this is my sickness!
- 那洁癖呢？ - 那只是好习惯
- What about the obsessive cleaning?     - That's just good sense.
噢
Ow!
- 你还好吗？ - 亲爱的 我还好
- You okay?     - No, honey, I'm okay.
甩一甩 哎 不能甩 不能甩 不能甩
Shake it off. Oh, no shaking. No shaking. No shaking.
我的天 我不能玩了
Oh, my God. I can't play.
- 所以你要弃权了？ - 麦克赢了吗？
- So you forfeit?     - Mike wins?
我不敢相信 我输了
I can't believe it. I lost.
- 不 你没有   - 什么？
- No, you didn't.     - What?
- 因为我要帮你玩   - 你不能这样做
- Because I'm gonna play for you.     - You can't do that.
没关系 我不在乎 我打败的是其中哪一个
It's okay. I don't care which of them I beat.
好 我们要把 那个球拍带回家 先生
Okay, we're taking that paddle home, mister.
- 亲爱的 你没有必要这样做   - 有 我有必要
- Honey, you don't have to do this.     - Yes, I do.
我或许无法理解 你为什么一定要赢…
I may not understand why you have to win so badly...
但是如果这对你很重要 对我就很重要
...but if it's important to you, it's important to me.
因为我爱你
Because I love you.
但是你很逊啊
But you suck.
不客气 甜心
You're welcome, sweetheart.
好 麦克 我们快开始吧 一球定生死
All right, let's get this over with. Sudden death.
- 赢得这一分的人就算赢了   - 好的
- Whoever wins this point, wins.     - Okay.
- 天啊 你真棒   - 这好像是在看色情片一样
- Oh, my God. You're good.     - It's like watching porn.
而这就是这样结束的
And that's how it's done.
我的天啊… 这实在太惊人了
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. That was so amazing.
你是何时…
Well, when did you...?
等等 我差点忘了 输家
Hold on, I almost forgot. Loser.
- 你是何时开始不逊的？ - 我从没逊过我只是不想让你…
- When did you stop sucking?     - I never sucked. I just didn't want you...
- 知道我有多厉害   - 为什么？
- to know how good I was.     - Why?
- 不知道   - 这真是太棒了
- I don't know.     - Well, this is so great.
- 现在我们可以参加双打比赛了   - 这就是为什么
- Now we can enter doubles tournaments.     - That's why.
- 他们还在找我们吗？ - 对
- They still looking for us?     - Yeah.
酒保说他们分成两组搜索队伍
The bartender said they split up into two search parties.
草食组跟肉食组
The herbivores and the carnivores.
我们古生物学家实在酷不起来
You know, we, as a group, are not the coolest.
喔 小心
Oh, look out.
- 我想他们没有看到我们   - 没错
- I don't think they saw us.     - I don't think they did.
我刚刚想告诉你一些事
So I started to tell you something earlier. Um...
我跟乔伊分手 还有别的原因
There was another reason that I realized it was time to end it with Joey.
我有点惊觉到我开始对某人…
I kind of realized I was starting to have feelings...
有一点感觉
for someone else.
喔
Oh.
我可以问是谁吗？
And can I ask who?
我想你知道是谁
I think you know.
我也认为我知道 但过去… 我对这种事的判断都错了 所以…
I think I know too, but I've been really wrong about this stuff in the past, so...
- 我很抱歉 我们不能这样   - 好吧
- I'm sorry, we can't.     - All right. All right.
说真的 你才刚跟我最要好的朋友分手
I mean, you just went out with my best friend, you know?
我只是认为这样很不好
I just think it would be a really, really bad idea.
不过或许也不会 我是说…
Or not. I mean...
怎么了？
What?
哦
Oh.